hekongjm.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Hekongjm

**Introduction.** This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. These privacy practices apply to the website located at the www.hekongjm.com and related hekongjm websites, pages, applications, and mobile applications (collectively, the "Site"), that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated directly by us or by our affiliated companies. We encourage you to read the privacy policy carefully and take the time to get to know our practices ? and if you have any questions contact us. 

**Privacy Shield.**  

####  Information hekongjm Collects 

hekongjm collects information to provide a more efficient service to all our users. We collect information in the following ways: 

**Information you give us.** For example, when you interact with our Site by making a purchase or subscribing to an email list, we can ask for information including the following; personal information, like your first and last name, company name, email address, postal address, phone number, and credit card number. We also collect passwords, password hints, and similar security information used for authentication and account access. 

**Information hekongjm gets from your use of our services**

hekongjm collects data about how you and your device interact with hekongjm and our services. For example, we collect: 

  * _Product use data_. We collect data about the features you use, the items you purchase, and the web pages you visit. 

  * _Device data_. We collect data about your device and the network you use to connect to our products. It includes data about the operating systems and other software installed on your device. It may include IP address, device identifiers (such as the IMEI number for phones), regional and language settings. 

  * _Error reports and performance data_. We collect data regarding the performance of the products and any problems you experience with them. This data helps to diagnose problems in the services you use, and to improve our service and provide solutions. Depending on your service and settings, error reports can include data such as the type or severity of the problem, details of the software or hardware related to an error, contents of files you were using when an error occurred, and data about other software on your device. 

  * _Support Data_. When you engage hekongjm for support, we collect data about you and your hardware, software, and other details related to the support incident. Such data includes contact or authentication data, the content of your chats and other communications with hekongjm support. 

####  Accountability for Onward Transfer 

If hekongjm discloses Personal Data covered by this Policy to a non-agent third party, it will do so consistent with any notice provided to data subjects and any choice they have exercised regarding such disclosure. hekongjm will only disclose Personal Data to third-party agents that have given us contractual assurances that they will provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the principles underlying the Privacy Shield (the Principles) and that they will process Personal Data for limited and specific purposes consistent with any consent provided by the individual. If hekongjm has knowledge that a third party to which it has disclosed Personal Data covered by this Policy is processing such Personal Data in a way that is contrary to this Policy and/or the Principles, hekongjm will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop such processing. In such case, the third-party is liable for damages unless it is proven that hekongjm is responsible for the event giving rise to the violation. 

####  Reasons We Share Personal Data 

We may share your personal data with your consent or as necessary to provide our services. When you provide payment data to make a purchase, we will share payment data with banks and other entities that process payment transactions or provide other financial services, and for fraud prevention and credit risk reduction. In addition, we share personal data among hekongjm-controlled affiliates and subsidiaries. hekongjm may use from time to time a limited number of third-party service providers, contractors, and other businesses to assist us in providing our solutions to our customers or for the purposes described in this statement. In such cases, these companies must abide by our data privacy and security requirements and are not allowed to use personal data they receive from us for any other purpose. We may also disclose personal data as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets. 

####  The Purpose for which Information is Collected 

hekongjm uses the data we collect for two basic purposes, described in more detail below: (1) to operate our business and provide (including improving and personalizing) the services we offer, and (2) to send communications, including promotional communications. 

**Providing and Improving Our Services**. We use data to carry out your transaction and to provide our services to you.  We also use data to diagnose service problems, troubleshoot issues, and provide other customer care and support services. We use data collected to continually improve our services, including adding new features or capabilities, such as using error reports to improve security features and determining what new features to prioritize. Data is also used to develop aggregate analysis and business intelligence that enable us to operate, protect, make informed decisions, and report on the performance of our business. 

**Communications**. We use data we collect to deliver and personalize our communications with you. For example, we may contact you by email or other means to inform you when a subscription is ending, let you know when security updates are available, remind you about items left in your online shopping cart, update you or inquire about a service or repair request, invite you to participate in a survey, or tell you that you need to take action to keep your account active. Additionally, you can sign up for email subscriptions and choose whether you wish to receive promotional communications from hekongjm by email, SMS, physical mail, and telephone. 

####  Transparency and Choice 

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. For example, our customers can: 

  * Review and control certain types of information tied to your hekongjm Account by using the hekongjm control panel. 

  * Control who you share information with through your hekongjm Account. 

  * Take information associated with your hekongjm Account out of many of our services. 

You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. 

####  Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information 

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. 

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup systems). 

We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems. 

####  Security of Personal Data 

hekongjm is committed to protecting the security of your personal data. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When we transmit highly confidential data (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption.
